export const DivisionQuestion = {
    question21: {
        question: "90/10 = ?",
        options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
        answer: 9
    },
    question22: {
        question: "150/5 = ?",
        options: [30, 25, 20, 15],
        answer: 30
    },
    question23: {
        question: "200/8 = ?",
        options: [24, 25, 26, 27],
        answer: 25
    },
    question24: {
        question: "84/7 = ?",
        options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
        answer: 12
    },
    question25: {
        question: "144/12 = ?",
        options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
        answer: 12
    },
    question26: {
        question: "60/5 = ?",
        options: [11, 12, 13, 14],
        answer: 12
    },
    question27: {
        question: "48/6 = ?",
        options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
        answer: 8
    },
    question28: {
        question: "90/9 = ?",
        options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
        answer: 10
    },
    question29: {
        question: "70/10 = ?",
        options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
        answer: 7
    },
    question30: {
        question: "120/6 = ?",
        options: [20, 21, 22, 23],
        answer: 20
    },
    question31: {
        question: "150/3 = ?",
        options: [40, 45, 50, 55],
        answer: 50
    },
    question32: {
        question: "64/8 = ?",
        options: [7, 8, 9, 10],
        answer: 8
    },
    question33: {
        question: "32/4 = ?",
        options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
        answer: 8
    },
    question34: {
        question: "28/4 = ?",
        options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
        answer: 7
    },
    question35: {
        question: "225/15 = ?",
        options: [12, 13, 14, 15],
        answer: 15
    },
    question36: {
        question: "81/3 = ?",
        options: [25, 26, 27, 28],
        answer: 27
    },
    question37: {
        question: "60/12 = ?",
        options: [4, 5, 6, 7],
        answer: 5
    },
    question38: {
        question: "45/5 = ?",
        options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
        answer: 9
    },
    question39: {
        question: "16/4 = ?",
        options: [2, 3, 4, 5],
        answer: 4
    },
    question40: {
        question: "36/4 = ?",
        options: [7, 8, 9, 10],
        answer: 9
    },
    question41: {
        question: "55/11 = ?",
        options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
        answer: 5
    },
    question42: {
        question: "70/7 = ?",
        options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
        answer: 10
    },
    question43: {
        question: "36/6 = ?",
        options: [4, 5, 6, 7],
        answer: 6
    },
    question44: {
        question: "120/8 = ?",
        options: [13, 14, 15, 16],
        answer: 15
    },
    question45: {
        question: "150/10 = ?",
        options: [12, 13, 14, 15],
        answer: 15
    },
    question46: {
        question: "72/9 = ?",
        options: [7, 8, 9, 10],
        answer: 8
    },
    question47: {
        question: "110/11 = ?",
        options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
        answer: 10
    },
    question48: {
        question: "96/12 = ?",
        options: [8, 7, 6, 5],
        answer: 8
    },
    question49: {
        question: "75/5 = ?",
        options: [12, 13, 14, 15],
        answer: 15
    },
    question50: {
        question: "180/9 = ?",
        options: [18, 19, 20, 21],
        answer: 20
    },
    question1:   {
      question: "10/2 = ?",
      options: [3, 4, 5, 6],
      answer: 5
    },
  question2:  {
      question: "24/3 = ?",
      options: [8, 5, 6, 7],
      answer: 8
    },
   question3: {
      question: "48/3 = ?",
      options: [9, 16, 11, 12],
      answer: 16
    },
   question4: {
      question: "44/4 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 11
    },
  question5:  {
      question: "625/25 = ?",
      options: [10, 25, 12, 13],
      answer: 25
    },
    question6: {
    question: "36/6 = ?",
    options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
    answer: 6
  },
question7: {
    question: "81/9 = ?",
    options: [7, 8, 9, 10],
    answer: 9
  },
question8: {
    question: "100/4 = ?",
    options: [20, 25, 15, 30],
    answer: 25
  },
question9: {
    question: "49/7 = ?",
    options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
    answer: 7
  },
question10: {
    question: "72/8 = ?",
    options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
    answer: 9
  },
question11: {
    question: "120/5 = ?",
    options: [20, 22, 23, 24],
    answer: 24
  },
question12: {
    question: "144/12 = ?",
    options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
    answer: 12
  },
question13: {
    question: "56/7 = ?",
    options: [7, 8, 9, 10],
    answer: 8
  },
question14: {
    question: "90/9 = ?",
    options: [9, 10, 11, 12],
    answer: 10
  },
question15: {
    question: "64/8 = ?",
    options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
    answer: 8
  },
question16: {
    question: "108/9 = ?",
    options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
    answer: 12
  },
question17: {
    question: "125/5 = ?",
    options: [20, 22, 24, 25],
    answer: 25
  },
question18: {
    question: "40/5 = ?",
    options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
    answer: 8
  },
question19: {
    question: "84/12 = ?",
    options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
    answer: 7
  },
question20: {
    question: "56/8 = ?",
    options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
    answer: 7
  }

}
